<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#Collectors on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/tags/collectors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #Collectors on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/tags/collectors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CPU Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-cpu-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-cpu-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     cpu-#.cpu-idle.value Number of jiffies the CPU spent idle. average jiffies 0 none none yes no no   cpu-#.cpu-interrupt.value Number of jiffies the CPU spent processing hardware interrupts. average jiffies 0 none none yes no no   cpu-#.cpu-nice.value Number of jiffies the CPU spent processing low priority user threads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collectd</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/</guid>
      <description>Collectd’s Write HTTP plugin can be used to configure collectd to send data to Metricly. If you need additional information about setting up Collectd, view their wiki.
Configuration 1. Copy API Key in Metricly  From the top navigation menu, click Integrations. Click the collectd card. Data collection should already be enabled, and a unique API key for your account has already been generated. Copy the API key.  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collectors</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/agents/linux-agent/linux-collectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/agents/linux-agent/linux-collectors/</guid>
      <description>There are three ways to configure the Linux Agent default collectors: via the BaseCollector, as a combination of individual collectors, or with just the SimpleCollector. This guide outlines their differences and how to use each; however, we encourage you to try the new SimpleCollector.
Using the Simple Collector netuitive-diamond/src/collectors/simple
Where the base or individual collectors include more data (which may be less useful or actionable), this SimpleCollector guarantees a cleaner streamlined experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collectors</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DF Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-df-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-df-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     df-&amp;lt;mount&amp;gt;.df_complex-free.value Free disk space in bytes. average bytes 0 none none yes no no   df-&amp;lt;mount&amp;gt;.df_complex-reserved.value Disk space reserved for root user in bytes. average bytes 0 none none yes no no   df-&amp;lt;mount&amp;gt;.df_complex-used.value Used disk space in bytes. average bytes 0 none none yes no no    Computed    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max BASE CORR UTIL     metricly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disk Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-disk-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-disk-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     disk-&amp;lt;dn&amp;gt;.disk_merged.read Number of merged reads per second. average operations/second 0 none none yes no no   disk-&amp;lt;dn&amp;gt;.disk_merged.write Number of merged writes per second. average operations/second 0 none none yes no no   disk-&amp;lt;dn&amp;gt;.disk_octets.read Bytes read per second. average bytes/second 0 none none yes no no   disk-&amp;lt;dn&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flume</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/flume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/flume/</guid>
      <description>Flume collects and aggregates all of your log files distributed across your environment. Metricly can be used to monitor the performance of your Flume service.
Configuration  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors. Open the FlumeCollector.conf file. Change the enabled setting to True. Update the req_host, req_port, and/or req_path settings as necessary. Save the configuration file and restart the Linux Agent.  Collector Options    Option Default Description     enabled FALSE Enable collecting Flume metrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Code Collector</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-code-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-code-collector/</guid>
      <description>HTTP status codes are useful diagnostic tools for a website to help determine if all content on a website is being delivered properly. Enabling the HTTP code collector for your preferred website will log every status code returned by the website. The first time a status code is returned, our Linux agent will create a metric for that code in Metricly; each subsequent time the status code is returned, another metric will begin to count how many times the code has been returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Collector</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-collector/</guid>
      <description>The HTTP Collector gathers statistics from an HTTP or HTTPS connection.
Prerequisites The Linux Agent is required before proceeding with the setup of the HTTP Collector. If you need to disable the Linux integration or view the unique API key assigned to your account, navigate to the Integrations page under the user account drop-down menu and click the integration designated as Infrastructure under the Integration column.
Update the Configuration File  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTPD</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/httpd/</guid>
      <description>The HTTP Collector gathers statistics from an HTTP or HTTPS connection.
Prerequisites The Linux Agent is required before proceeding with the setup of HTTPD. If you need to disable the Linux integration or view the unique API key assigned to your account, navigate to the Integrations page under the user account drop-down menu and click the integration designated as Infrastructure under the Integration column.
Update the Configuration File  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interface Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-interface-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-interface-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     interface-&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;.if_errors.rx Errors per second received. average errors/second 0 none none yes no no   interface-&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;.if_errors.tx Errors per second sent. average errors/second 0 none none yes no no   interface-&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;.if_octets.rx Bytes per second received. average bytes/second 0 none none yes no no   interface-&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;.if_octets.tx Bytes per second sent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JMX</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/jmx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/jmx/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites The Linux Agent is required before proceeding with the setup of HTTPD. If you need to disable the Linux integration or view the unique API key assigned to your account, navigate to the Integrations page under the user account drop-down menu and click the integration designated as Infrastructure under the Integration column.
Configuration  Download the Jolokia JVM JAR file. Move the downloaded file to the /opt/netuitive-agent/ directory. Pass the Java agent parameter into your application:  -javaagent:/opt/agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kafka</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/</guid>
      <description>Kafka is a publish-subscribe message queuing system that’s designed like a distributed commit log. Metricly can help monitor the performance and throughput of your Kafka server using our Kafka collector for the Linux agent. Kafka, Kafka Consumer Lag, and Zookeeper metrics are all collected using this collector.
Prerequisites The [Linux Agent][1] is required before proceeding with the setup of HTTPD. If you need to disable the Linux integration or view the unique API key assigned to your account, navigate to the Integrations page under the user account drop-down menu and click the integration designated as Infrastructure under the Integration column.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kafka Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/kafka-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/kafka-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Due to the sheer volume of Kafka metrics, the individual metrics won’t be documented here. Instead, this page outlines general properties for the groups of metrics.
Properties All Metrics Share:  Statistic: average Min: 0 CORR: no UTIL: no BASE:  On for most metrics Off for metrics matching the following regexes: ^kafka.cluster.* ^kafka\.utils\..* ^kafka\.log\..*(LogEndOffset|LogStartOffset)$ ^kafka\.controller\.((?!broker-\d).).* ^kafka\.consumer_group\.((?!consumer_lag$).)*$   Metrics That End With Percent:  Unit: percent Max: 1  Metrics With Bytes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kafka in Docker</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/kafka-in-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/kafka/kafka-in-docker/</guid>
      <description>Getting the Jolokia agent running in a Kafka container requires three additional modifications to the docker run command. To illustrate the modifications needed, we’re going to assume that your docker run command looks like this initially:
docker run -p 2181:2181 -p 9092:9092 --env ADVERTISED_HOST=`docker-machine ip\`docker-machine active\`` --env ADVERTISED_PORT=9092 spotify/kafka  Update Docker Run Command  Make the Jolokia JAR file available to the container by passing it in as a mounted volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Load Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-load-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-load-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     load.load.longterm The is the average run queue size over the past 15 minutes. average queued processes 0 none none yes no no   load.load.midterm The is the average run queue size over the past 5 minutes. average queued processes 0 none none yes yes no   load.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-memory-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-memory-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     memory.memory-buffered.value Memory being used by buffers; this memory is available to be freed forapplications to use, should they need it. average bytes 0 none none yes no no   memory.memory-cached.value Memory being used by caches; this memory is available to be freed forapplications to use, should they need it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-code-collector/http-code-collector-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-code-collector/http-code-collector-metrics/</guid>
      <description>This collector tracks per URL which response codes are received as well as the number of times each code was received as two separate metrics. The Response Code List metric’s value is the literal response code number at the time it was received. The Response Code count increments each time a response code is received; this means that you won’t have a metric for every response code until your web site serves up that response code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-collector/http-collector-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/http-collector/http-collector-metrics/</guid>
      <description> Collected    Friendly Name Fully Qualified Name (FQN) Description Statistic     Servers Http Time servers.[hostname].http.[url].time Time to download the page in microseconds. average   Servers Http Size servers.[hostname].http.[url].size Size of the page received in bytes. bytes    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/httpd/httpd-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/httpd/httpd-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name (FQN) Type Units Statistic Min Max Sparse Data Strategy (SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     httpd..BusyWorkers GAUGE count average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..BytesPerReq GAUGE bytes average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..BytesPerSec GAUGE Bps average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..CleanupWorkers GAUGE count average 0 none none yes no no   httpd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Resource Collector</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/process-resources-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/process-resources-collector/</guid>
      <description>The Process Resources Collector can be used to collect CPU- and Memory-type metrics on a per-process level.
Prerequisites  Linux Agent  Configure Update the Configuration File  Navigate to the collectors folder, opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors. Open the ProcessResourcesCollector.conf file. Change the enabled setting to True. For each process you’d like to monitor, include the following below the [process] section:  [[process_name]] name = &amp;quot;.*regex-statement.*&amp;quot;  Example
[[nginx]] name = ^nginx  5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Processes Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-processes-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-processes-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     processes.fork_rate.value Number of processes per second being forked. average forks/second 0 none none yes no no   processes.ps_state-blocked.value Number of processes in a blocked state. A process that is blocked is onethat is waiting for some event, such as a resource becoming available orthe completion of an I/O operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNMP</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/snmp-interface-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/snmp-interface-collector/</guid>
      <description>The SNMP Collector is used to allow Metricly to monitor the performance of SNMP-enabled devices using a set of specified OIDs. The collector can gather data from as many devices as necessary by adding additional configuration sections under the [devices] header.
Prerequisites You should have SNMP set-up and your community string ready prior to activating the SNMP collector.
 Linux Agent  Configure  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNMP Interface</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/snmp-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/snmp-collector/</guid>
      <description>The Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) Interface collector is used to allow the Linux agent to monitor the performance of remote SNMP-enabled devices like routers and switches. The collector can gather data from as many devices as necessary by adding additional configuration sections under the [devices] header; see the example below for details.
Prerequisites You should have SNMP set-up and your community string ready prior to activating the SNMP collector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TCP</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/tcp-collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/tcp-collector/</guid>
      <description>The TCP Collector collects metrics on TCP stats.
Prerequisites  Linux Agent  Configure  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors. Open the TCPCollector.conf file. Change the enabled setting to True. Save the configuration file and restart the Linux Agent.  Collector Options    Setting Default Description Type     allowed_names ListenOverflows, ListenDrops, TCPLoss, TCPTimeouts, TCPFastRetrans, TCPLostRetransmit, TCPForwardRetrans, TCPSlowStartRetrans, CurrEstab, TCPAbortOnMemory, TCPBacklogDrop, AttemptFails, EstabResets, InErrs, ActiveOpens, PassiveOpens list of entries to collect, empty to collect all str   byte_unit byte Default numeric output(s) str   enabled False Enable collecting these metrics bool   gauges CurrEstab, MaxConn list of metrics to be published as gauges str   measure_collector_time False Collect the collector run time in ms bool   metrics_blacklist None Regex to match metrics to block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uptime Metrics</title>
      <link>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-uptime-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://metriclyhelpsite.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/collectd/collectd-uptime-metrics/</guid>
      <description> Collected    Fully Qualified Name(FQN) Description Statistic Units Min Max Sparse Data Strategy(SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     uptime.uptime.value Number of seconds since the system was last booted. max seconds 0 none none yes no no    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>