<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Httpd on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/httpd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Httpd on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/httpd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTPD</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/httpd/</guid>
      <description>The HTTP Collector gathers statistics from an HTTP or HTTPS connection.
Prerequisites The Linux Agent is required before proceeding with the setup of HTTPD. If you need to disable the Linux integration or view the unique API key assigned to your account, navigate to the Integrations page under the user account drop-down menu and click the integration designated as Infrastructure under the Integration column.
Update the Configuration File  Navigate to the collectors folder, /opt/netuitive-agent/conf/collectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/httpd/httpd-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/httpd/httpd-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name (FQN) Type Units Statistic Min Max Sparse Data Strategy (SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     httpd..BusyWorkers GAUGE count average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..BytesPerReq GAUGE bytes average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..BytesPerSec GAUGE Bps average 0 none none yes no no   httpd..CleanupWorkers GAUGE count average 0 none none yes no no   httpd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache HTTPD Policies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/alerts-notifications/policies/default-policies/apache-policies-httpd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/alerts-notifications/policies/default-policies/apache-policies-httpd/</guid>
      <description>Linux Apache HTTPD – Depressed Traffic Volume 30 min httpd..ReqPerSec has a lower baseline deviation WARNING The number of requests per second has been lower than expected for at least the past 30 minutes.     Linux Apache HTTPD – Elevated Traffic Volume 30 min httpd..ReqPerSec has an upper baseline deviation WARNING The number of requests per second has been higher than expected for at least the past 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>