<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rabbitmq on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/tags/rabbitmq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rabbitmq on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/tags/rabbitmq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/rabbitmq/rabbitmq-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/rabbitmq/rabbitmq-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Collected    Fully Qualified Name (FQN) Type Units Statistic Min Max Sparse Data Strategy (SDS) BASE CORR UTIL     rabbitmq.cluster.nodes GAUGE count average 0 none none no no no   rabbitmq.cluster.partitions GAUGE count average 0 none none no no no   rabbitmq.health.disk_free GAUGE bytes average 0 none none yes no no   rabbitmq.health.disk_free_limit GAUGE bytes average 0 none none no no no   rabbitmq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RabbitMQ Policies</title>
      <link>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/alerts-notifications/policies/default-policies/rabbitmq-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/alerts-notifications/policies/default-policies/rabbitmq-policies/</guid>
      <description>Policy names are prefixed with RabbitMQ –
    Policy name Duration Conditions Category Description     Depressed Message Count 30 min rabbitmq.queue_totals.messages has a lower baseline deviation WARNING The number of messages across all queues has been lower than expected for at least the past 30 minutes.   Elevated Memory Usage 30 min rabbitmq.health.mem_used has an upper baseline deviation WARNING Memory usage has been higher than expected for at least the past 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rabbitMQ</title>
      <link>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/rabbitmq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cranky-lalande-9d501c.netlify.com/integrations/collectors/rabbitmq/</guid>
      <description>Rabbit MQ is a message broker that manages queues between message producers and consumers. Metricly can be used to monitor your RabbitMQ server’s queuing performance.
Prerequisites  Linux Agent  Before editing the configuration file, you should verify the RabbitMQ management module is enabled. If the module is not enabled, do the following:
 If the package is installed globally, type this into your command prompt:
rabbitmq-plugins enable rabbitmq_management  If the package is installed in a directory, type this into your command prompt instead:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>