<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Azure on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft Azure on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:08:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-installation/</guid>
      <description>1. Create a Microsoft Azure Integration Card  From the top navigation menu, select Integrations. Click the Microsoft Azure card. In a separate, new tab, open the Azure portal.  The following instructions were created using the Azure portal not the classic portal. Instructions vary depending on which portal you’re using.
 2. Create an Active Directory Application in Azure  Once in the Azure portal, click Azure Active Directory from the left side menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Guest OS Diagnostic Metrics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-enable-guest-os-diagnostic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-enable-guest-os-diagnostic/</guid>
      <description>Azure Virtual Machines will share boot diagnostic metrics by default, which are a small subset of core metrics. To enable Guest OS diagnostic (basic) metrics that provide more information about your machine, you’ll need to follow these steps (depending on your situation):
Enable Basic Metrics on Existing VM  In Azure, navigate to Virtual machines. Select a virtual machine. Another window with options will open. Select Diagnostic settings. Under Configure required settings, select the checkbox next to Basic metrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filter Elements</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-filter-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/microsoft-azure/azure-filter-elements/</guid>
      <description>You can filter what Azure elements are included in Metricly’s monitoring by using regex to match key-value pairs. Metricly offers opt-in (include) or opt-out (exclude) element filtering.
Using opt-in filtering  In your Azure portal, create or choose an existing tag (key-value pair). Then, assign the tag to the Azure elements you do not want Metricly to monitor. In Metricly, navigate to your Azure integration card. Expand the element types you want to filter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>