<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Directory Page on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/directory-page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Directory Page on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/directory-page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>Visualize your data in Metricly with dashboards.You can use the default, pre-packaged integration dashboards or create and customize your own using widgets. Default dashboards are not editable.
View a Dashboard  Click on Dashboards in the main menu.
or Navigate to Dashboards &amp;gt; Manage Dashboards.  Edit a Dashboard Editing an existing dashboard can involve managing the layout of a dashboard, changing the dashboard’s settings, or manipulating the time frame setting/refresh interval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>1. Watch Our Product Demo There’s no faster way to get acquainted with the UI than by watching the demo video. This tour covers both the Cost and Monitoring products, including topics like: the EC2 recommendation report, the Utilization Boxplot report, and the Cost report.
2. Register an Account You’re excited to right-size your environments and lower their costs. You’ve done all your research, and you’re ready to try Metricly’s 21-day free trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reports/</guid>
      <description> Reports provide a quick glance at some of the most important parts of your environment, including utilization, policy violation, and estimated cost of your inventory. Report Explorer allows you to toggle between different reports on the elements in your environment.
Required Integrations for Metricly Reports    Report Name AWS w/ Cost Explorer AWS w/ CloudWatch AWS Cost w/ Detailed Billing List Price Estimation w/out AWS Cost Time from activation to first report     AWS Services Cost x    Immediate   Resource Utilization  x   Immediate   EC2 Cost  x x x 1 day   RDS Cost  x x  1 day   S3 Cost  x x  1 day   EC2 Recommendations  x x x 1 week   ASG Recommendations  x x x 1 week    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/</guid>
      <description>afafa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:08:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/agents/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collectors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/collectors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widgets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/widgets/</guid>
      <description>This guide includes a list of all widget types available, their options, and the actions you can take. To take full advantage of widgets, you should strategize how to tag, group, and visualize the data in your environment. General knowledge on elements and the behavior of your metrics is strongly encouraged before making a custom dashboard.
Move Widgets  Hover over the widget’s title to select. The header turns gray and your cursor is replaced with  when a widget is selected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/analytics/</guid>
      <description>Metricly uses advanced analytics to monitor your environment and proactively notify you when problems occur. There are 3 basic data types that Metricly uses to do so:
 Raw data: Data collected from a third party integration that has not been interpreted, or aggregated, by Metricly. Because it has not been aggregated, raw data does not contribute to event creation. Aggregate data: Data collected from an integration that has been interpreted by Metricly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>