<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inventory on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inventory on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Element Detail Panel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-element-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-element-detail/</guid>
      <description>The Element Detail panel displays tabs for the metric summary, policies, and relationships associated with the selected element.
Summary Tab The Summary tab displays a dashboard full of select widgets to highlight the most important details of the selected element.
Policies Tab The Policies tab offers the same functionality as the Policies Page except the Policies tab only displays policies that include the selected element in the policy’s scope. Below is a picture of an EC2’s policies tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Navigation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-main-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-main-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Select Filters Contains several filters where you can search for element names, element types, tags, attributes, collectors, and more. Expand the More filter to see additional filters; select a filter to add it to the list of active filters.
Save Filters Filters you create in the navigation panel can be saved.
 Click  SAVE. Provide a filter name and click  or hit enter. Share filter if desired via  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickbar Actions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-quickbar-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-quickbar-actions/</guid>
      <description>The inventory page allows you to quickly navigate through all of your elements, sort, and perform bulk actions. The Inventory Explorer displays all the elements in your environment that were processed in the last hour. Elements are removed from the elements table roughly seven hours after an associated datasource is disabled.
Use the Quick Bar Select the elements you’d like to edit using the checkboxes on the far left of each row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort Elements</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-sort-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-sort-elements/</guid>
      <description>Select two or more elements and then click View Metrics to open multiple elements on the Metrics page. The Elements table initially has six columns:
 Type: Shows icon for an element’s type. You can see all the icons here. Name: Name of the element. Data Collection: The percentage of metrics that were collected in the last analytics cycle (5 minutes).If no metrics were collected, there could have been an issue with collection or too many metrics were collected, which forces Metricly to not collect any metrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start or Stop Maintenance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-startstop-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-startstop-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>You can place elements into maintenance mode from the Inventory Explorer or via the Metricly CLI (Command Line Interface). While an element is in maintenance mode, learning for that element is disabled (i.e. no contextual or baseline bands will be displayed) and events will not be generated for the element.
 Open the Inventory Explorer. Select the check box next to as many elements as desired. Click Start or Stop Maintenance at the top of the Inventory Explorer table.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>