<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elements on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/elements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elements on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/elements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Inventory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/</guid>
      <description>Your inventory is the elements that make up your environment, from your java virtual machines to your Amazon EC2s. Metricly’s Inventory Explorer allows you to view and search the elements in your inventory.
About Elements The physical or logical components that Metricly monitors are called elements. An element can be a physical entity, such as a server or network element, a virtual entity, such as a transaction, or a business entity, such as a company traded on the stock market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optional Config</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/aws-integration/aws-optional-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:08:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/aws-integration/aws-optional-config/</guid>
      <description>Change Element Display Names You can change how certain elements’ names are displayed in the application to help distinguish between each instance, e.g., you have 15 EC2 instances with the same name and want to know the difference between each.
 Under the Include Types list, expand the desired type.
 Beneath the Tag Key field, click Advanced. A menu expands.
 Hover next to Element Name; an edit icon will appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optional Config</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/integrations/agents/linux-agent/linux-optional-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:08:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/integrations/agents/linux-agent/linux-optional-config/</guid>
      <description>Changing Element Display Names You can change the display name of certain elements to help distinguish between each instance.
 Navigate to Integrations &amp;gt; Linux Integration. Click Advanced; a menu expands.  Click the Element Name field to edit it. Type the desired name into the field.  An element name of ${meta.originalName} would resolve to whatever name comes in with the original element payload before it would be replaced with the optional element name template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copy a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/copy-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/copy-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Copy a Dashboard A quick and easy way to create a customized dashboard is to copy a defaulted one and edit it.
 Navigate to Dashboards &amp;gt; Select Dashboard Name. Click on  &amp;gt; Copy.  Rename the Dashboard. Edit the widgets by clicking … &amp;gt; Settings or Delete.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create New Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/create-new-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/create-new-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Create a New Dashboard  Navigate to Dashboards on the main navigation menu. Click New Dashboard. Type a name for the dashboard. Click Save. You’ll be taken to the Widget Library, where you can add a widget.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/delete-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/delete-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Via Manage Dashboards You can delete a dashboard by navigating to Dashboards &amp;gt; Manage Dashboards and clicking  . Via Any Dashboard You can delete custom dashboards directly on their page by clicking  &amp;gt; Delete Dashboard. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duration &amp; Refresh Intervals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/duration-refresh-intervals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/duration-refresh-intervals/</guid>
      <description>Adjusting the dashboard’s Duration or Refresh Interval affects the data displayed in widgets on your dashboard.
Change Duration Edit the Duration setting for the dashboard in the sub navigation menu.
 Choose a Duration (past) value. Select an Ending value (default is Now). The data then automatically reloads to reflect your changes.   Two widgets behave differently in regards to the Duration setting:
 Metric Status Widget: Current Values in Metric Status widgets are not affected by the Time Frame setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/favorite-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/favorite-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Favorited dashboards display as a drop-down list under Dashboards in the main top navigation menu.
Favorite a Dashboard  Navigate to the Dashboard menu (or Dashboard &amp;gt; Manage Dashboards). A list of all the dashboards available in your tenant appears. Click  next to a dashboard to favorite it.  Unfavorite a Dashboard Repeat the above process and click  to unfavorite the dashboard. This removes the dashboard from your quick drop-down list in the top navigation menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/share-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/share-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>You can configure a dashboard to be either public or private. By default, dashboards you create are private.
Make a Dashboard Public  Navigate to the Dashboards menu. Select All Dashboards &amp;gt; My Dashboards. A list of the dashboards you have created appears.  Toggle Shared to active (green) to make the dashboard public.  Make a Dashboard Private To make a dashboard private, repeat the above steps and toggle Shared to inactive (grey).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Element Detail Panel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-element-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-element-detail/</guid>
      <description>The Element Detail panel displays tabs for the metric summary, policies, and relationships associated with the selected element.
Summary Tab The Summary tab displays a dashboard full of select widgets to highlight the most important details of the selected element.
Policies Tab The Policies tab offers the same functionality as the Policies Page except the Policies tab only displays policies that include the selected element in the policy’s scope. Below is a picture of an EC2’s policies tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Navigation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-main-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-main-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Select Filters Contains several filters where you can search for element names, element types, tags, attributes, collectors, and more. Expand the More filter to see additional filters; select a filter to add it to the list of active filters.
Save Filters Filters you create in the navigation panel can be saved.
 Click  SAVE. Provide a filter name and click  or hit enter. Share filter if desired via  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickbar Actions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-quickbar-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-quickbar-actions/</guid>
      <description>The inventory page allows you to quickly navigate through all of your elements, sort, and perform bulk actions. The Inventory Explorer displays all the elements in your environment that were processed in the last hour. Elements are removed from the elements table roughly seven hours after an associated datasource is disabled.
Use the Quick Bar Select the elements you’d like to edit using the checkboxes on the far left of each row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort Elements</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-sort-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-sort-elements/</guid>
      <description>Select two or more elements and then click View Metrics to open multiple elements on the Metrics page. The Elements table initially has six columns:
 Type: Shows icon for an element’s type. You can see all the icons here. Name: Name of the element. Data Collection: The percentage of metrics that were collected in the last analytics cycle (5 minutes).If no metrics were collected, there could have been an issue with collection or too many metrics were collected, which forces Metricly to not collect any metrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start or Stop Maintenance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-startstop-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/inventory/inventory-startstop-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>You can place elements into maintenance mode from the Inventory Explorer or via the Metricly CLI (Command Line Interface). While an element is in maintenance mode, learning for that element is disabled (i.e. no contextual or baseline bands will be displayed) and events will not be generated for the element.
 Open the Inventory Explorer. Select the check box next to as many elements as desired. Click Start or Stop Maintenance at the top of the Inventory Explorer table.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>