<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dashboards on Metricly Docs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dashboards on Metricly Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Copy a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/copy-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/copy-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Copy a Dashboard A quick and easy way to create a customized dashboard is to copy a defaulted one and edit it.
 Navigate to Dashboards &amp;gt; Select Dashboard Name. Click on  &amp;gt; Copy.  Rename the Dashboard. Edit the widgets by clicking … &amp;gt; Settings or Delete.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create New Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/create-new-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/create-new-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Create a New Dashboard  Navigate to Dashboards on the main navigation menu. Click New Dashboard. Type a name for the dashboard. Click Save. You’ll be taken to the Widget Library, where you can add a widget.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/delete-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/delete-dashboard/</guid>
      <description> Via Manage Dashboards You can delete a dashboard by navigating to Dashboards &amp;gt; Manage Dashboards and clicking  . Via Any Dashboard You can delete custom dashboards directly on their page by clicking  &amp;gt; Delete Dashboard. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duration &amp; Refresh Intervals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/duration-refresh-intervals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/duration-refresh-intervals/</guid>
      <description>Adjusting the dashboard’s Duration or Refresh Interval affects the data displayed in widgets on your dashboard.
Change Duration Edit the Duration setting for the dashboard in the sub navigation menu.
 Choose a Duration (past) value. Select an Ending value (default is Now). The data then automatically reloads to reflect your changes.   Two widgets behave differently in regards to the Duration setting:
 Metric Status Widget: Current Values in Metric Status widgets are not affected by the Time Frame setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/favorite-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/favorite-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Favorited dashboards display as a drop-down list under Dashboards in the main top navigation menu.
Favorite a Dashboard  Navigate to the Dashboard menu (or Dashboard &amp;gt; Manage Dashboards). A list of all the dashboards available in your tenant appears. Click  next to a dashboard to favorite it.  Unfavorite a Dashboard Repeat the above process and click  to unfavorite the dashboard. This removes the dashboard from your quick drop-down list in the top navigation menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share a Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/share-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/data-visualization/dashboards/share-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>You can configure a dashboard to be either public or private. By default, dashboards you create are private.
Make a Dashboard Public  Navigate to the Dashboards menu. Select All Dashboards &amp;gt; My Dashboards. A list of the dashboards you have created appears.  Toggle Shared to active (green) to make the dashboard public.  Make a Dashboard Private To make a dashboard private, repeat the above steps and toggle Shared to inactive (grey).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>